<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<sceneConfigContainer>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>0</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Start</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>You wake up with a headache... You hear an old Iron Maiden song:
			#...To this day I guess I'll never know
			Just why they let me go
			But I'll never go dancing no more
			'Till I dance with death... #
			You turn off the tape, and start to find food and ammunition for your rifle...
		</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 1</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>1</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 2</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>2</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 3</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>3</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>1</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Search</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>After 10 minutes of search, you realize a crater that is left from the early on bombardments. Suddenly, something pushes you into the crater. Your leg is broken and all your weapons are out of your reach. You are left with nothing but your Swiss Army Knife in your pocket. You hear hummings all around... They come closer and closer... 'I wish I was a zombie.' is all what comes out of your mouth, when all the zombies making those noises come at you.
		</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 2</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>2</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 3</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>3</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 4</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>4</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>2</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Market</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>You go to the market. Even if you have to kill a couple of zombies on the way, your rifle and a fireaxe that you found in the ruins don't let you down. After you make sure that you have canned food in your bag that will last for a couple of days, it suddenly crosses to your mind that the market could possibly have a depository. Then you find a library card on the ground, you think some people might have hidden in the library and survived. Also you realize that your ammunition is in decline.</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 3</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>3</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 4</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>4</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 5</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>5</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>3</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Police Station</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>You go to the police station. There are many things that remind you of the days before the epidemic. A happy family picture, a birthday cake (half-eaten), a pack of cigars (very premium quality). However, those civilized days are over now. Nowadays there is just one valid virtue: TO SURVIVE... You go down into the armory, then you take lots of 5.56 mm bullets along with some grenades and put them into a somewhat large bag.</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 4</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>4</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 5</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>5</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 6</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>6</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>4</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>The Library</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>The library looks like a ruin. Scattared books on the ground and many human corpses at the corridors. 'Fortunately these corpses don't walk.' you say. But nobody laughes at your joke. There is nothing useful here, but there could be in the other parts of the building...</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 5</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>5</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 6</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>6</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 7</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>7</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>5</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Lower Floor</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>The lower floor is full of zombies. You immediately hold onto your rifle and although you manage to stick the brain of some of them all on the wall, it does not take you too long to realize that in narrow areas like this corridor the rifle isn't so efficient. Then you hold up your axe, but it's too late... The last idea in your mind is of the happy family you were at your elementary school graduation...</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 6</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>6</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 7</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>7</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 8</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>8</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>6</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Roof</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>You get to the roof. Looking at the ruins of the city from the scope of your rifle, you finish some of the zombies off. When you look through the horizon, something attracts your attention. A group of survivors fight against the zombies in ruins, and they win. By the way, you recognize only two big buildings that aren't in ruins: Sports' Complex and Cultural Center. Maybe there are some survivors in them.</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 7</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>7</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 8</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>8</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 9</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>9</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>7</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Outside</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>You go outside. There is a disgusting smell because of the
			corpses. You feel like vomitting. Then, you pass through the sea of
			the corpses, and you reach the city center. You see a destroyed and
			half-eaten corpse of a parachuter at the top of monument.Looking at
			the zombie corpses around him, you think that he resisted the attack
			of the zombies well, even though it was not enough for him. 'He must
			have been a hard soldier in his life' you say. The zombie corpses
			around the man proove that. There are two buildings that are not in
			ruins: the Sport Hall and the Cultural Center.</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 8</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>8</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 9</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>9</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 10</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>10</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>8</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Cultural Center</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>Cultural Center is a place surrounded fully by the zombie corpses. Apparently, it has been defended bravely. Yet it's forsaken now. When you pass the corridors, you miss the old days when people enjoyed the art. Everything was changed so suddenly. Two months ago, you listened to a recital of your favorite musician there.You feel like it has been ages. There is a backdoor and a basement in the building. Also, there is an amphitheatre outside.</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 9</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>9</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 10</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>10</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 11</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>11</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>9</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Sport Hall</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>You come across a few of the survivors at the Sport Hall. They help you with food and ammunition. The people that have nothing in common are all together here, all struggling to survive. An old, wise looked man among them gives you an advice: 'Survive, young man, nowadays this is very hard for us.</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 10</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>10</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 11</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>11</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 12</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>12</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>10</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Outside</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>You go outside. In one of the buildings, you find the note that explains that there are some survivors at the Sports' Complex. After more research, you find an old radio. Broadcast saying that: 'The last call for non-infected survivors! Three days later, all of the city will be erased from the map by nuclear weapons. All survivors who want to live, must reach the rescue point which is in the south of city hall.'</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 11</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>11</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 12</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>12</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 13</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>13</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>11</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>For the People, by the People</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>You stay with the people. It's very hard to get adapted to this new life. Life now goes in shifts. In the mornings, the people immune to the virus, loot the abandoned markets. In the nights, the other people repair the barricades. In a loot party, you suddenly see a sparkle while observing the horizon from a market's roof. THIS IS A HELICOPTER! Maybe the last hope for you and the people with you. However,you can double the good news after searching the market's depository..</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 12</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>12</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 13</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>13</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 14</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>14</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>12</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Selfish</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>Even though you feel remorseful for your selfishly taken decision, you don't care much. 'I took your advice, old man.', you think. When you reach the rescue zone, you see that the helicopter has been destroyed. After an intensive zombie attack, too many well-armored soldiers turned into zombies. You have no chance anymore, you will pay the price of your selfhishness, with your life.
		</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 13</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>13</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 14</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>14</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 15</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>15</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>
	<sceneConfig>
		<sceneIndex>13</sceneIndex>
		<sceneHeadline>Rescue</sceneHeadline>
		<sceneText>People say that they heard the broadcast announce, and they have to leave this city in three days. You get on the road all together. You're on the front line, because you're immune. Your voyage is very hard, but you reach the rescue zone. While you go to one of the non-infected zones, you think that life is still worth living.</sceneText>
		<westButtonText>To Scene 14</westButtonText>
		<westButtonSceneIndex>14</westButtonSceneIndex>
		<centerButtonText>To Scene 15</centerButtonText>
		<centerButtonSceneIndex>15</centerButtonSceneIndex>
		<eastButtonText>To Scene 16</eastButtonText>
		<eastButtonSceneIndex>16</eastButtonSceneIndex>
	</sceneConfig>

</sceneConfigContainer>